Pete Welding collection, 1958-1995
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 8: Sound recordings
  - Subseries 4: Compilations of dubbed commercial recordings
    - Standing Ovation - Count Basie Orchestra (Dot 25938); That Latin Beat: Antobal's Latin All-Stars Conducted by Chico O'Farrill (Dot 25445) (tape side 1); Goin' Places - Margaret Whiting (Dot 25072); Dori Howard Sings, with the Eddie Costa Quartet and Don Elliott Quintet (Dot 3230) (tape side 2)
      00:30:35 CBO perform their next piece "Blue and Sentimental"
      00:35:06 CBO perform "Every Tub"
      00:38:05 The start of the next instrumental selection called "Corner Pocket"
      00:44:03 The next instrumental piece titled "The Kid from Red Bank"
      00:46:36 The next selection by CBO titled "One O'clock Jump"
      00:48:22 Chico O'Farrill (CF) conducting Antobal's Latin All-Stars. The first piece they perform is "Una Aventura Mas"
      00:50:39 The beginning of the next instrumental piece called "Astronaut Special"
      00:53:21 "Voodoo Moon" by CF
      00:56:05 "Playtime in Brazil" by CF
      00:58:24 A performance of "Pachanga Universal" (Eugenio Fondeur)
      01:00:36 The next piece with voice and accompaniment titled "Fiesta en El Solar
      01:00:34 End
      Start Begins with Margaret Whiting singing a rendition of "The Gypsy in My Soul" (J. Mandel)
      00:02:29 Voice and accompaniment of "Sentimental Journey" (Mandel)
      00:05:33 The selection "Any Place I Hang My Hat Is Home" (Frank Comstock)
      00:08:18 The start of the song titled "I'm Gonna Move to the Outskirts of Town" (Skip Martin)
      00:10:43 Introduction to the song "Gone With the Wind" (Pete King)
      00:12:42 The start of "Runnin' Wild" (Pete Rugolo)
      00:14:27 The selection "Between the Devil and the Deep Blue Sea" (Rugolo)
      00:16:37 Introduction to the song "Somewhere Over the Rainbow" (Marty Paich)
      00:19:47 The start of "Hit the Road to Dreamland" (Comstock)
      00:22:20 The selection "East of the Sun and West of the Moon" (King)
      00:25:02 The introduction to "Song of the Wanderer" (Martin)
      00:27:29 The selection "Home (When Shadows Fall)" (Paich)
      00:30:08 The song titled "The Moon Was Yellow" with Dori Howard singing the remainder of the pieces. She is joined by Eddie Costa and the Don Elliott Quintets
      00:32:36 The start of "My One and Only Love"
      00:35:18 Introduction to the next song, "Here I am in Love Again"
      00:38:29 The song titled "I Get a Kick out of You"
      00:41:08 Introduction to the next song titled "Lonely Love"
      00:43:48 The selection "Mean to Me"
      00:46:01 The start of the song "How Long Has This Been Going On?"
      00:48:41 The song titled "Duke's Place"
      00:51:18 Introduction to "You're Not Alone"
      00:54:26 Introduction to the next song titled "Monday"
      00:56:26 The next selection called "Stop, Look and Run"
      01:00:16 The song titled, "Mood Indigo"
      01:03:52 End
    - Blues 78s, #11; Peggy Seeger, undated, AFC 2011/053: SR412; RXH 4652; 1 sound tape reel (01:00:32): analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      Logger's note: Dubs of commercial recordings by various singers, including Peggy Seeger, Furry Lewis, Memphis Minnie, and others.
      Start "Cumberland Gap" by Peggy Seeger
      00:02:04 "The Lady of Carlisle" by Peggy Seeger
      00:06:16 "The Deer Song" by Peggy Seeger
      00:09:08 "Come All Ye Fair and Tender Maidens" by Peggy Seeger
      00:12:12 "I Never Will Marry" by Peggy Seeger
      00:14:53 "Devilish Mary" by Peggy Seeger
      00:16:55 "The Fair Maid Freed By the Shore" by Peggy Seeger
      00:19:21 "Soldier's Joy" by Peggy Seeger
      00:20:19 "Shady Grove" by Peggy Seeger
      00:21:37 "Georgia Buck" by Peggy Seeger
      00:22:37 "The Wife of Usher's Well" by Peggy Seeger
      00:27:13 "Saturday Blues" by Ishman Bracey
      00:30:46 "Left Alone Blues" by Ishman Bracey
      00:34:28 "Kassie Jones" (part 1), by Furry Lewis
      00:37:37 "Kassie Jones" (part 2), by Furry Lewis
      00:40:47 "Honey" by Bo Carter
      00:43:38 "What You Want Your Daddy to Do" by Bo Carter
      00:46:45 "I'm talking About You" by Memphis Minnie (very poor sound quality)
      00:49:22 "Me And My Chauffeur Blues" by Memphis Minnie
      00:52:09 "Can't Afford To Lose My Man" by Memphis Minnie
      00:54:42 "Please Set A Date" by Memphis Minnie
      00:57:30 "True Love" by Memphis Minnie
      01:00:32 End
    - Blues 78s, #12, undated, AFC 2011/053: SR410; RXH 4650; 1 sound tape reel (01:04:01): analog, 3 3/4 ips, mono; 7 in.
      Logger's note: Dubs of commercial recordings by various singers.
      Start "Mama's Advice" by Peetie Wheatstraw (poor sound quality)
      00:03:26 "Police Station Blues" by Peetie Wheatstraw (poor sound quality)
      00:06:40 "Midnight Blues" by Peetie Wheatstraw (poor sound quality)
      00:10:08 "Johnnie Blues" by Peetie Wheatstraw (poor sound quality)
      00:13:00 "Deep Sea Diver" by Leroy Henderson (poor sound quality)
      00:15:53 "Low Mellow Man Blues" by Leroy Henderson (poor sound quality)
      00:18:53 "F.D.R. Blues" by Champion Jack Dupree (poor sound quality)
      00:21:35 "God Bless Our New President" by Champion Jack Dupree (poor sound quality)
      00:24:22 "South Bound Water" by Lonnie Johnson (poor sound quality)
      00:27:08 "Back Water Blues" by Lonnie Johnson (poor sound quality)
      00:30:44 "Bo Weevil Blues" by Madame "Ma" Rainey; accompanied by Lovie Austin
      00:33:36 "Cotton Crop Blues" by James Cotton
      00:36:40 "Charity Blues" by Gene Gilmore (poor sound quality)
      00:39:19 "Brome Street Blues" by Skoodle Dum Doo and Sheffield (poor sound quality)
      00:42:16 "West Kinney Street Blues" by Skoodle Dum Doo and Sheffield (poor sound quality)
      00:45:01 "Pretty Man Blues" by Luella Miller (poor sound quality)
      00:47:40 "Dago Hill Blues" by Luella Miller (poor sound quality)
      00:50:40 "Love Me Or Let me Be" by James (Beale Street) Clark.
      00:53:32 "Get Ready To Meet Your Man" by James (Beale Street) Clark
      00:56:12 "Dew Drop Alley Stomp" by Sugar Underwood
      00:59:34 "Davis Street Blues" by Sugar Underwood
      01:02:43 "Pig Meat Blues" by Ardell Bragg (poor sound quality; the song ends abruptly)
      01:04:01 End
    - Blues 78s, #13, undated, AFC 2011/053: SR411; RXH 4651; 1 sound tape reel (00:50:41): analog, 3 3/4 ips, mono; 7 in.
      Start "She's Gone Blues" by Barbecue Bob
      00:03:32 "Bad Time Blues" by Barbecue Bob
      00:06:48 "Crooked Woman Blues" by Barbecue Bob
      00:09:49 "'Fo Day Creep" by Barbecue Bob
      00:13:06 "Thinkin' Funny Blues" by Barbecue Bob
      00:16:29 "Motherless Chile Blues" by Barbecue Bob
      00:19:50 "My Mistake Blues" by Barbecue Bob
      00:22:11 "How Long Pretty Mama" by Barbecue Bob
      00:26:40 "Barrel House Blues" by Ed Andrews
      00:29:50 "Time [sic] Ain't Gonna Make Me Stay" by Ed Andrews
      00:32:56 "Shake It Up And Go" by Tommy McClennan
      00:35:56 "I Love My Baby" by Tommy McClennan
      00:39:03 "Stack Of Dollars" by Joe Williams
      00:41:51 "Mellow Apples" by Joe Williams
      00:44:42 "The O. P. A. Blues" by Dossie (Georgia Boy) Terry
      00:47:59 "Furlough Blues" by Dossie (Georgia Boy) Terry
      00:50:41 End
    - Blues 78s dubs (Kansas Joe - Memphis Minnie), undated, AFC 2011/053: SR392; RXH 4633; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:11): analog, 7 1/2 ips, full track, stereo; 7 in.
    - Blues 78s dubs, 120 (Georgia Bill - Clarence Green), undated, AFC 2011/053: SR393; RXH 4634; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:41): analog, 7 1/2 ips, full track, stereo; 7 in.
    - Mercury blues dubs, 1949, 1952, AFC 2011/053: SR397; RXH 4638; 1 sound tape reel (00:28:16): analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      Start "Sittin' Here Wonderin'" - Luther Stoneham (Mercury 8275; 1949)
      00:03:43 "January 11, 1949 Blues" - Luther Stoneham (Mercury 8275; 1949)
      00:06:21 "Hey Hey" - Big Bill Broonzy (Mercury 8271; 1952)
      00:09:17 "Walkin' The Lonesome Road" - Big Bill Broonzy (Mercury 8271; 1952)
      00:12:37 "Hit The Road Again" - Sunnyland Slim (Mercury 8264; 1952)
      00:15:51 "Gin Drinkin' Baby" - Sunnyland Slim (Mercury 8264; 1952)
      00:18:51 "Gone With The Wind" - Lightnin' Hopkins (Mercury 8293; 1952)
      00:21:30 "She's Almost Dead" - Lightnin' Hopkins (Mercury 8293; 1952)
      00:25:08 "Sad News From Korea" - Lightnin' Hopkins (Mercury 8274; 1952)
      00:28:16 End
    - Blues dubs (no titles), undated, AFC 2011/053: SR383; RXH 4624; 1 sound tape reel (Side 1: 01:35:56, Side 2: 01:36:14): analog, 3 3/4 ips, mono; 7 in.
      Start "Gypsy Woman" - Muddy Waters
      00:02:31 "Little Anna Mae" - Muddy Waters
      00:04:59 unidentified male singer ("I go get up in the morning, go find me some coo coo place to go/this old house have done got rocky and I can't live there no more/Everybody told me lives in your neighborhood") [possibly the same singer as on the next song]
      00:07:34 "Do It If You Want To" - unidentified male singer [possibly the same as the preceding song]
      00:09:56 "Decoration Day" - Sonny Boy Williamson
      00:12:37 "Love Me, Baby" - Sonny Boy Williamson
      00:15:47 "I'm In A Traveling Mood" - Andrew Tibbs and Dozier Boys
      00:18:41 "The Holidays Are Overs" - Andrew Tibbs
      00:21:42 "Bilbo Is Dead" - Andrew Tibbs, with Dave Young's Orchestra
      00:24:30 "Union Man Blues" - Andrew Tibbs, with Dave Young's Orchestra
      00:27:35 "Carolina Blues" [?] ("Now that [?] rain or shining [?] don't the clouds look awful gray/I believe the Carolina blues and trouble is gonna follow me to my grave"
      00:30:22 "First Time I Met the Blues" - unidentified male singer, with piano
      00:33:06 "Say Pretty Mama (I'm Goin' to Kansas City)" - Sloke and Ike [Charlie Slocum and Ikey Robinson]
      00:35:41 "Slocum Blues" - Sloke and Ike [Charlie Slocum and Ikey Robinson]
      00:38:29 "Back Water Blues" - Ruby Smith
      00:41:14 "He's Mine, All Mine" - Ruby Smith
      00:43:50 "Harlem Gin Blues" - Ruby Smith
      00:46:42 "Why Don't You Love Me Anymore" - Ruby Smith
      00:49:19 Lyrics: "Where was you last night daddy when I knocked upon your door/... there was a pallet on your floor"
      00:52:04 Lyrics: "I took you in baby when you didn't have a cent/well, you wouldn't buy no groceries, didn't have to pay no rent"
      00:54:51 Lyrics: "winds are breakin' my heart/And I'm frantic because I'm in the dark/I know I love you because the rain wrote in on my window babe"
      00:57:15 "Rocks in My Bed" - unidentified male singer
      00:59:47 "Rocks in My Bed" [snippet only]
      00:59:54 "My First Love Blues" - Tampa Red
      01:02:44 "Let Me Play With Your Poodle" - Tampa Red
      01:05:18 Lyrics: "I fool around with you [?] clothes are gone [?]/ain't nothing in the drug store [?] help you none"
      01:08:01 snippet of the preceding song
      01:08:18 Lyrics: "My telephone is out of order, and my doorbell refuse to ring"
      01:11:02 "Streamline Train" - Cripple Clarence Lofton
      01:13:41 "Crying Mother Blues" - Cripple Clarence Lofton with Red Nelson
      01:16:13 Lyrics: "From Detroit to the river...to the break of day/if I don't see the woman I love somebody's gonna have to bury me/you can catch a Detroit special, you can ride most anywhere"
      01:19:07 Lyrics: "I am sitting here thinking all day long [?]/my best friend has gone and won't be back no more/nights and days I pray that I'll find her in this world somewhere/I have looked the whole world over, the Lord must not have heard my prayer"
      01:21:53 Lyrics: "Early in the morning, 'bout the break of day/I done moved out of the apartment where my baby used to stay"
      01:24:33 Lyrics: "My mother she dead and my father too/and I don't know what in this whole wide world to do/I gonna lay my head on some Southern railroad iron"
      01:27:10 Lyrics: "Baby please don't go/back to New Orleans, you know I love you so/turn your lamp down low"
      01:29:51 "Break 'Em On Down" - unidentified male singer, with guitar and harmonica
      01:32:50 Lyrics: "...since my good man has gone" [poor source recording condition]
      01:35:36 End
      Start "This Is Your Last Chance" - Memphis Minnie
      00:02:57 "Pig Meat on the Line" - Memphis Minnie
      00:05:25 "Goin' Down Slow" - unidentified male singer
      00:08:15 Lyrics: "Murder, murder in the first degree/[police] this woman is killing me/it ain't the way she wears her lipstick or the powder on her face, just the knowledge of the weakness in the whole human race"
      00:10:54 Lyrics: "I ain't going down there [?] myself/why don't hear you talking pretty mama/I don't care you're gone, go on get somebody else/no sun gonna shine in my back door someday"
      00:14:09 Cool Drink of Water Blues - Tommy Jones
      00:17:37 Lyrics: "Now that I wake up she taken sick/before she dies lord lord before she dies/but I'm so glad poor girl had [?]/before she dies, lord knows before she dies"
      00:20:04 Lyrics: "I say hey short man, quit knocking on my door, 'cause I'm four months behind and you ought to know I'm ain't gonna join that on [?] no more/well the last time I fed you I give you a $5 bill and the next time I fed you, you were running [?]"
      00:22:38 Lyrics: "Hey what do you want your man to do/I rob and steal and make every [?] too/for my breakfast, give me half a cup of tea/[?] I ain't gonna work for you no more"
      00:25:37 Lyrics: "I woke up this morning [?] took a [?] around my baby's bed/I got her face to the wall [?] not a word she said"
      00:28:27 Lyrics: "My baby just mistreat me night and day/she mistreat the poor man just to pass the doggone time away/and baby what have I done was wrong/mistreat me baby and drove me away from my home"
      00:31:21 Lyrics: "I said never mind, never mind baby, I got my doggone eyes on you/[?] pretty baby, do like I want you to do/when I was sick and down you drove me from your door/you know I was a poor man, sleeping out in the ice and snow"
      00:34:20 "Drifting Heart" - Chuck Berry
      00:37:03 "Roll Over Beethoven" - Chuck Berry
      00:39:20 "Step It Up and Go" - Blind Boy Fuller
      00:42:09 "Little Woman You're So Sweet" - Blind Boy Fuller
      00:44:46 Lyrics: "Mama here come your root man, open the door and let him in/it is just about time you're using your good root again/your skin is getting bumpy and your skin looks over bad"
      00:47:49 "Blue Sky Is My Blanket" - unidentified performer
      00:50:43 unidentified female singer ("...Let's get drunk and suck/I know your other man is out of town, my other woman she's not around/now is the time to break 'em down") [same performer as the next song]
      00:53:42 unidentified female singer ("I can't satisfy you no matter how I try to/maybe it's someone else you care for/you say you'd give the world for someone to care and live for, baby someone else to care/I try to pacify you in every way I know but I think you're happy you're raising hell for more") [same performer as the preceding song]
      00:57:02 Lyrics: "I've been around the world, I've covered a lot of space/haven't found no one yet that can ever take your place/that ain't it, baby I need your love/now [?] who you thinking of"
      00:59:02 Lyrics: "I'm walking by myself, I hope you understand I just want to be your loving man/love you, yes I love you with all my heart and soul/wouldn't mistreat you for my weight in gold/you know I love you, you know it's true/give you all of my loving/what more can I do"
      01:01:44 Lyrics: "I was early one morning mama, I was on my way to [?]/just when I got to know you, [?] break my mama's rules"
      01:04:47 unidentified male singer [inaudible; fast beat]
      01:07:59 "Happy Home Blues" - Mississippi Matilda
      01:10:38 "Hardworking Woman Blues" - Mississippi Matilda
      01:13:26 "Mr. Pawn Broker" - B. B. King [?]
      01:15:54 Lyrics: "You're the cutest thing in my life that I've ever witnessed to/when the woman I love [?] out there too/I told her to take it easy baby"
      01:18:30 Lyrics: "I know a gal, her name is Betty Hobbs [?]/make good money on all her jobs/just cutting them clothes/she never did hurry, she just kept on cutting them clothes/day in and day out, she didn't want for a thing, she didn't use nothing but an easy swing"
      01:21:21 Lyrics: "Early one morning when the possum left his den/[?] my baby came creeping in/[record skips here] mama tell me what's the matter now"
      01:24:20 [inaudible; too much static]
      01:27:08 Lyrics: "I ain't nothing but a hobo, won't somebody help me carry my load/...I have been in the jungle three long nights and days"
      01:30:17 Lyrics: "Ain't it a shame, ain't it a shame, low down dirty shame/my baby wrote for me [?] won't let me ride this train/goodbye old Memphis, goodbye to the state of Tennessee/I'm going home to my baby"
      01:33:26 "Working Man (Doing the Best I Can)" - Peetie Wheatstraw
    - Blues dubs (Mercury), undated, AFC 2011/053: SR409; RXH 4649; 1 sound tape reel (00:15:39): analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
      Logger's note: Dubs of commercial recordings by Lightnin' Hopkins.
      Start "Let Me Fly Your Kite"
      00:03:46 "Ain't It A Shame"
      00:06:48 "Crazy 'Bout My Baby"
      00:09:36 "You Do Too"
      00:12:42 "Every Body's Down On Me"
      00:15:39 End
    - Blues dubs (Blind Sammie - Georgia Bill), undated, AFC 2011/053: SR394; RXH 4635; 1 sound tape reel (00:35:11): analog, 7 1/2 ips, stereo; 7 in.
    - Blues dubs (Ishman Bracey, Yank Rachell, and others), undated, AFC 2011/053: SR378; RXH 4619; 1 sound tape reel (00:32:02): analog, 7 1/2 ips, full track, stereo; 7 in.
      Logger's note: Dubbed commercial recordings by several artists.
      Start "Trouble Hearted Blues" - Ishman Bracey
      00:03:26 "The Four (Sic) Day Blues" - Ishman Bracey
      00:06:50 "Loudella Blues" - Yank Rachell
      00:09:43 "Rainy Day Blues" - Yank Rachell
      00:12:37 "Little Leg Woman" - Poor Joe Williams
      00:15:48 "Somebody's Been Borrowing That Stuff" - Poor Joe Williams
      00:19:02 "Providence Help The Poor People" - Poor Joe Williams
      00:22:14 "49 Highway Blues" - Poor Joe Williams
      00:25:30 "Ain't Seen No Whisky" Sleepy John Estes
      00:28:55 "Cannonball Blues" Furry Lewis
      00:32:02 End
    - Blues dubs, undated, AFC 2011/053: SR382; RXH 4623; 1 sound tape reel (Side 1: 01:35:12, Side 2: 00:36:54: analog, 3 3/4 ips, mono; 7 in.
      Start "She Wants to Rattle Me All the Time" - Jimmie Gordon ("I got a woman/she can't be beat/she's tailor made and she's too sweet/she's a rattle snaking mama/she's a rattle snaking mama/she's a rattle snaking mama/she wants to rattle me all the time")
      00:02:50 Lyrics: "I got the number runner blues/and every time I see a policeman I almost jump out of my shoes/standing on the corner, standing on the corner/wasn't doing nothing wrong/that policeman [?] took me by my arm"
      00:05:30 Lyrics: "Every time a woman says she loves you please don't put pay that no mind/he's just jiving you just to pass away the time"
      00:08:38 "Delia's Gone ("Delia, I'm so all alone/the only girl I ever loved but now you dead and gone/and lord you gone, you gone, Delia you gone")
      00:11:43 Lyrics: "Come all day, come on rainy day/come on rainy day/... and blow my blues away/give me chicken when I'm hungry, lightning' when I'm dry/ give me chicken when I'm hungry, white lightnin' when I'm dry/and a real kind woman and heaven when I die"
      00:14:32 "Roll 'Em Pete" ("I got a girl, she lives up on that hill/well that fool tried to quit but I love her still/she's got eyes like diamontine shine like Klondike gold/every time she loves me she sends my mellow soul")
      00:17:26 Lyrics: "I got those traveling blues, 'bout you catch a train and ride/I got those traveling blues, bout to catch a train and ride/'cause when I'm a'riding I'm not satisfied/Dixieland is where the south begins/ I'm going to [?] my Pullman and ride that [?] in"
      00:20:22 "Nappy Headed Blues" - Helen Humes
      00:23:17 "Garlic Blues" - Helen Humes
      00:26:07 "Today I Sing the Blues" - Helen Humes
      00:28:52 "Jumpin' on Sugar Hill" - Helen Humes
      00:31:41 "Don't Fall in Love With Me" - Helen Humes
      00:34:41 "Somebody Loves Me" - Helen Humes
      00:36:59 "Jet Propelled Papa" - Helen Humes
      00:39:33 "Blue and Sentimental" - Helen Humes
      00:42:34 "Hard Drivin' Mama" - Helen Humes
      00:45:25 "If I Could Be With You" - Helen Humes
      00:47:58 unidentified song performed by Helen Humes (Lyrics: "I've got my eyes on you/I can't seem like I'm looking but I got my eyes on you seeing everything you do/I watch your brown shoulders and that great big smile" [chorus throughout song] "hey hey baby/hey hey baby/ hey hey baby")
      00:50:22 "Laziest Gal in Town" - Helen Humes
      00:52:51 "My Life My Way" - Helen Humes
      00:55:52 "I Ain't in the Mood" - Helen Humes
      00:58:21 "Helen's Advice" - Helen Humes
      01:01:01 "Airplane Blues" - Helen Humes
      01:03:23 Lyrics: "Sometimes your heart is aching and you stood about all that you can/it's time to move your belongings, and find you another man"
      01:06:42 Lyrics: "Don't you know your chances always been good honey, you were blind and could not see/Your chances was good baby, you were blind and could not see/all [?] picked a good woman [?] not when you passed by me"
      01:09:14 "Nickel's Worth of Liver Blues" - Edith Johnson
      01:11:49 "Honey Dripper Blues" - Edith Johnson
      01:14:44 "Barrel House Flat Blues" - Mary Johnson
      01:17:37 "Key to the Mountain Blues" - Mary Johnson
      01:20:25 unidentified male singer (Lyrics: "What you going to do, can't get no jam/same to the women, also the man/Me and old Jones, can't get along/he ain't my friend, 'cause he can get dead")
      01:23:23 unidentified male singer (Lyrics: "I think my baby don't speak to me no more/... and knocked her out of the door/take my baby I'm done telling lies and I caught her telling lies")
      01:26:30 "Church Bell Blues" - Luke Jordan
      01:29:33 "Cocaine Blues" - Luke Jordan
      01:32:39 "Whitewash Station Blues" - Memphis Jug Band
      01:35:12 End
      Start "Stealin' Stealin'" - Memphis Jug Band
      00:03:09 "One of These Mornings" - unidentified female singer (Lyrics: "Kind of feeling blue sighing over you/you may think I've prove [?] me wrong when I sing this song/one of these mornings you're gonna wake up and find me gone/one of these mornings I tell it won't be long")
      00:06:07 unidentified female singer (Lyrics: "You start to forget me, I'm going to stop loving you/you know you mistreated me that will never do/now haven't I always been true/man I'm a-faithful you, man ain't no good/'cause you walked away"(
      00:08:34 "Sun Gonna Shine" [?] - unidentified female singer (Lyrics: "...Oh lonely mine ... sits just the [?] blue") [loud static / inaudible]
      00:11:30 "Fire in the Mountain Blues" - Thelma La Vizzo
      00:14:21 Lyrics: "I met a woman in west Texas, she had been left by herself alone/I bought a [?] [car] for [all three] where I wasn't even known/she fell for me a ragged stranger in the drizzling rain"
      00:17:07 Lyrics: "I get up early every morning to toil the whole day through/baby wouldn't be so hard if I was getting up from beside of you/I'm so lonely without you baby, I can't be satisfied"
      00:20:10 "Denomination Blues" [or "That's All]" - unidentified singer
      00:25:28 "Sundown Blues" - Alec Johnson (vocal) Kansas Joe McCoy (guitar)
      00:28:14 "Miss Meal Cramp Blues" - Alec Johnson
      00:31:03 Lyrics: "When the sun get hot/[?] because they can't work it no more" [inaudible]